export const questions = [
    {
        question: 'If soccer is called football in England, what is American football called in England?',
        choice1: 'American football',
        choice2: 'Combball',
        choice3: 'Handball',
        choice4: 'Touchdown',
        answer: 'American football'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name for the Jewish New Year?',
        choice1: 'Hanukkah',
        choice2: 'Yom Kippur',
        choice3: 'Kwanza',
        choice4: 'Rosh Hashanah',
        answer: 'Hanukkah'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?',
        choice1: 'Ron Weasley',
        choice2: 'Neville Longbottom',
        choice3: 'Draco Malfoy',
        choice4: 'Hermione Granger',
        answer: 'Draco Malfoy'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which animal does not appear in the Chinese Zodiac?',
        choice1: 'Dragon',
        choice2: 'Rabbit',
        choice3: 'Dog',
        choice4: 'Hummingbird',
        answer: 'Hummingbird'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?',
        choice1: 'China',
        choice2: 'Ireland',
        choice3: 'Brazil',
        choice4: 'Italy',
        answer: 'Brazil'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which boyband sings the song “I Want It That Way”?',
        choice1: 'One Direction',
        choice2: 'Backstreet Boys',
        choice3: 'NSYNC',
        choice4: 'New Kids On The Block',
        answer: 'Backstreet Boys'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
        choice1: 'Van Gogh',
        choice2: 'da Vinci',
        choice3: 'Picasso',
        choice4: 'Monet',
        answer: 'da Vinci'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who wrote the songs for The Lion King? ',
        choice1: 'Stevie Wonder',
        choice2: 'Celine Dion',
        choice3: 'Elton John',
        choice4: 'Phil Collins',
        answer: 'Elton John'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many degrees are in a circle?',
        choice1: '150',
        choice2: '180',
        choice3: '630',
        choice4: '360',
        answer: '360'
    },
    {
        question: 'The UK is made up of the following countries: England, Ireland, Wales, and…',
        choice1: 'France',
        choice2: 'Hungary',
        choice3: 'Scotland',
        choice4: 'Austria',
        answer: 'Scotland'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many rings are there in the Olympic symbol?',
        choice1: '5',
        choice2: '7',
        choice3: '4',
        choice4: '9',
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is celebrated on December 26th?',
        choice1: 'the day after Christmas',
        choice2: 'Harvest Day',
        choice3: 'National Dog Day',
        choice4: 'Boxing Day',
        answer: 'Boxing Day'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the company that published the Mario Kart video game?',
        choice1: 'Nintendo',
        choice2: 'Electronic Arts (EA)',
        choice3: 'SEGA',
        choice4: 'Xbox',
        answer: 'Nintendo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which water sport is the official sport for the state of Hawaii?',
        choice1: 'water polo',
        choice2: 'swimming',
        choice3: 'water skiing',
        choice4: 'surfing',
        answer: 'surfing'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which actor performs music under the stage name Childish Gambino?',
        choice1: 'Donald Glover',
        choice2: 'Will Smith',
        choice3: 'Frank Ocean',
        choice4: 'Tyler, The Creator',
        answer: 'Donald Glover'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the black metal band who released "Transilvanian Hunger" in 1994?',
        choice1: 'mgla',
        choice2: 'Darkthrone',
        choice3: 'Wedard',
        choice4: '359',
        answer: 'Darkthrone'
    },
    {
        question: 'Sodium bicarbonate is used in the kitchen as what?',
        choice1: 'salt',
        choice2: 'sugar',
        choice3: 'baking soda',
        choice4: 'vinegar',
        answer: 'baking soda'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many eyes do most spiders have?',
        choice1: '8',
        choice2: '2',
        choice3: '10',
        choice4: '6',
        answer: '8'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many time zones are there in the world?',
        choice1: '20',
        choice2: '16',
        choice3: '12',
        choice4: '24',
        answer: '24'
    },
    {
        question: 'What animal is associated with ancient Egypt?',
        choice1: 'lion',
        choice2: 'hummingbird',
        choice3: 'cat',
        choice4: 'rabbit',
        answer: 'cat'
    }
]